Hi everyone. Good to be back.
>> Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> Just don't know how you approach free
you have to really get out there. I
don't know if you went in as the default
being. You might be somewhere else or
you always thought you'd be back.
>> Yeah, we we went into it with a pretty
open mind about what could happen just
because, you know, you can't really
control who offers and like whether the
Bucks were going to offer or not. But um
you know I'm we're both our whole family
is really happy with how it worked out
and and being back here with a lot of
people we love and um you know loving
playing football here. So yeah just it
was it was pretty straightforward I'd
say and it and went amazing.
>> Kate, you've got another offensive
coordinator again. Tell me about what
your interactions have been like with
Zack Robinson and what his vision is for
not just you but the tight end position
in in his offense. really positive and
uh I mean first of all just from from
people who aren't him I've only heard
great things um about just the way he
operates and how detailed he is and the
person that he is but just getting to
talk with him he's uh you know just
seems really excited about the the
personnel that we have to to run his
offense and how he envisions it and um
and I don't I don't think he's the type
of guy who's like who's fixed on what
we're going to do like he's gonna make
get to to where we're all put in
positions to succeed based on the player
we are. But um you know just really love
getting to talk to him and and hear his
vision for what we can be.
>> You look back to last year, the tight
end position and the passing game as a
whole, not just you, but you know, it
was you and Devin the only touchdown
scorers and that happened late in the
year. Do you feel like the tight end
position is going to be emphasized a
little bit more maybe this year than it
than it was last year? perhaps more to
like what Liam Cohen was doing with you
guys in 2024.
>> I don't know. It's I mean I I don't try
to to focus on those sorts of things. Um
but I do have full confidence in what
[snorts] uh Coach Robinson's going to do
to put us all in positions to succeed.
And you know, I think the end result
will be, you know, us [snorts] scoring
more points and having more red zone
opportunities as a as a tight end group
and as an offense as a whole. uh because
it's clear we have to improve in in
those areas. But whether the the
touchdowns are are to me or to someone
else, you know, I I just want the our
offense to be humming and to have team
success.
>> What What did you think when you heard
that Mike was leaving and were you
surprised that Mike Evans left?
>> Yeah, I was surprised. Um you know, I
don't obviously you don't know the Bucks
without him just like as a fan watching
and you know, as a player. Um, but you
know, I'm so thankful for the time I got
to spend with him and just to learn from
him and you know, as you guys know
there, he's an amazing person, amazing
teammate, amazing player. So, definitely
sad he's not here, but I'll I'll be
rooting for him personally uh until we
end up playing the 49ers. But, um, yeah,
it was it was a surprise, I'd say.
>> What's your thoughts about what's left,
right? I mean, obviously Mike was a big
part of this offense, but you saw that
receiver room last year. You know what
you have in your room. So, just in terms
of of the potential and the production
that that you guys have had, what can
you do to pick that up? Obviously, it's
a big loss. Yeah, it's a huge loss, but
I have full confidence in in everyone
and especially, you know, I can't think
of anyone who's who's hurt during this
off season and just getting a full, you
know, offseason, the OTAAS together
thrown with Baker and um I think that
will be huge and you know, I have I have
all the confidence in the world in the
ability of those guys and you know,
there's I don't know if there's any
other mics in the league and so only one
team's going to get them, but we're all
going to to to pick up our our his slack
that he's leaving. And I I think, you
know, we might do some different things
offensively. Like, no one's going to
fill the exact role that Mike did, but
um you know, I like I said, I have full
confidence in in Coach Robinson to
maximize what we can do.
>> You mentioned Baker. How can your
connection with him evolve
to work with him?
>> Super excited. You know, Baker is
amazing person, amazing teammate also.
Um, but I just think the the time and
reps we get to spend together. Um, it
it's going to be huge. Again, just a
healthy off season. Um, and you know,
what is it now going to be three years
with him [snorts] and it's a it's a he's
just a great quarterback and you know, I
I think he's going to be fired up for
the opportunity we have. um having been
with Coach Robinson in the past and and
um I I'm just excited to keep working
with him. He's a huge draw to being here
in Tampa.
>> You've had a time you've had a time to
reflect, Kate, on last season. Um what
goes through your mind about what what
happened, the drop off after the
by-week? What what do you think were
some of the factors?
>> And it's it's hard to pinpoint one thing
and and I I first go to like what could
I I could have done personally to help
us. Um, and and again, I don't think it
was just one thing. Um, but I I'm sure
there are there are things we can do
week in week out to to help our level of
play, but I do think, you know, defense
has maybe started to to attack us a
little bit and um and we didn't respond
as well as we should have on on an
indivi individual level um mostly. And
so, uh, we're we're going to work as
hard as we can to fix that. Um, I know
I'm going to work my hardest to to step
up my game to be more consistent and and
better across the board. And I know each
guy in that locker room who's who's
coming back and who's coming in is going
to do so as well.
>> K, first time you didn't end your season
in the playoffs. How hungry do you think
that's going to make the team going into
the offse?
>> Really hungry. I mean, it's it it's hard
watching playoff football at home. like
I do it just, you know, because I'm a
fan of football and and I'm involved in
the games and wants to see I want to see
what happens, but as a competitor, um it
sucks. And so, um we know like as a
team, the players we have, that's where
we're supposed to be. We're supposed to
be in the playoffs competing for a Super
Bowl. And [snorts] you know, it's going
to take work in the offseason separating
ourselves from the other good teams
because there are a lot. Um we got to
separate ourselves, put in the work.
K, did you say you were you have been
throwing with Baker? Did you say that?
>> No, we we haven't thrown yet. No.
>> Have you seen him at all? How's he
doing? He seemed like he was a little
beat up this season. Have you seen him?
>> He's in good spirits. Yeah. Uh I think
spending time with family kind of
getting, you know, that reset that's
that's needed after a long season. And I
know it's hard like no one really sees
what quarterbacks do behind the scenes.
like maybe some of the Netflix series
you get some of that. Um, but he puts in
so much work each and every day and know
I'm glad he's rested a little bit and I
hope he continues to cuz you know I I
know once we get back to work he's going
to give it his all, be as detailed as
ever. Um, be as competitive as ever and
give us the best chance to win a Super
Bowl.
>> Ken, I know a lot of work goes into
getting here, right? [snorts] Getting to
that first contract. I don't know if
it's been a whirlwind, it's been a
grind. You've got a young family now.
Just just think about yourself like how
different life is for you and just where
you're at having grown, you know, your
family through here coming as a rookie
and then now it's totally different,
right?
>> Yeah, absolutely. It's it's really, you
know, humbling and emotional to think
about. Um, first of all, I just I have
to thank God for giving me the ability
to play football. um and and all the
things that could have gone right or
wrong to to get me to this point and my
my beautiful wife Sierra for supporting
me every step of the way. And um you
know we we got married before my senior
year of college and you know we we're
we're living in this crappy little
apartment in a crappy part of Seattle
and uh and we were so happy and we we
just talked about how like no matter you
know how far football goes or like you
know what type of money we earn like
we're we're living off of you know $300
after a stipend each month and like we
we just loved it and you know just
wanted to wanted that to never change.
And so now that you know this this
second contract is here, we're super
we're super humbled, but we don't want
it to like change how we are and what
our lives are like. And um again, I'll
I'll just thank a couple more people. My
my parents um my dad for um just
inspiring me to play football and just
developing that love. And uh and then my
mom for supporting me as well. and she
got me this big poster that she put in
my room of an NFL player running out of
the tunnel. And so she she inspired me
to live this dream and I'm here. So
>> you got that visual reminder all the
time.
>> Yeah, that's right. That's right. So
>> not that there Huskies in the building,
but ask about Jake Browning coming in
here, your memories with him and and
what it's like to be playing with him
again.
>> He's awesome. Um I like just reflecting
on that the past day like he's he's a
lot like Baker in a few different ways
just uh he's really really prepared a
great competitor like you you kind of
see how he's mildmannered off the field
but he's he's a really fiery competitor
>> and um just a great leader. So I'm I'm
really excited to work with Jake again
um and I'm excited to see him. Yeah.
>> He would have been your first college
quarterback.
>> Yes. Yeah.
Do
>> you and Baker talk much, Kate, about uh
red zone and and and you scoring more
touchdowns and being more of a target in
the red zone?
>> No. No. I I trust him to make the right
decision. And you know, if there's if
there's certain things we see with
certain plays that are installed that he
thinks I'm going to get the ball, like
we'll we'll talk about that. And that
happened many times last season and
>> [snorts]
>> um you know, just didn't happen till the
last game. That is what it is. But I,
you know, there's no reason to take it
personally or anything like that. Like I
said, I I trust Baker and his decision-
making and the preparation that he puts
in. Again, like he he works all day
every day to, you know, play his best on
Sunday.
>> You kind of do everything, but where
where would you like yourself to to
continue to improve specifically in your
game now that you're back?
>> Yeah, I mean, there's there's a few
things for sure. And then like you said,
like I I take pride in in being asked to
do everything a tight end could be asked
to do. And so, you [snorts] know, I want
to I want to work on being more dominant
in the run game. I think I I put maybe
my best tape out there on our last game
of the season, both in the run and pass
game. And so, I just felt really
confident in that and my my mental
process going into that game. So, just
wanting to build on that and then
obviously put in the time and reps in in
the off season to make sure, you know,
start the season well. [laughter]
>> [snorts]
>> Okay.
>> You never come off the field and you
haven't come off. What does that uh you
know, does that fatigue you at some
point? Do you do you need a little more
time to refresh in between downs? Like
or are you just like, "Hey, leave me out
there to do whatever. I'm I'm good."
>> Yeah. I I mean, that's that's how I love
playing football. Like I just I just
want to be out there and whatever job is
called upon like I I want to do it. And
you know, I respect coach's decision. If
they think someone else is is better for
a certain play, but then I'm going to
work as hard as I can to be the best
person for that play. And so, um, I
mean, that's what I did in high school.
That's where I got to in college, just
being on the field every single down.
And, you know, I want to keep that going
here.
>> You said you had everything you needed
in that Seattle apartment. So, does that
mean you're not going to be making any
big purchases coming up?
>> We don't plan on it. Um yeah, like we
said, we we uh we're happy with the the
way we live and you know, hope we can
change some other people's lives with
what we have, but um yeah, we're we're
happy. [snorts]
>> What's it like being a family of four
now?
>> It's it's incredible. It's a it's we've
talked about it. The adjustment from
from one to two is a little easier than
zero to one, but the the man-to-man
defense wears on you a little bit
>> playing zone. Yeah.
>> You call him Tenny?
>> Okay. What are your kids names?
>> This is Tanal right here. We call her
Tenny. Hi.
>> And Amos is our new son.
>> Get back.
>> Probably a good time to say hi.
>> How old?
>> Uh she's 20 months and Amos is five
weeks.
>> Snacking hands right now.
right over here on this side.
>> We're going to take a photo.